<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paradisus</title>
    <link>http://kmil31.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Paradisus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 15:37:10 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kmil31.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 15:37:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/coffee/</guid>
      
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Blacker than a moonless night, hotter and more bitter than hell itself, that is&amp;hellip; coffee&amp;rdquo;
Diego Armando
 I have suprised even myself. In previous times, I can count the amount of times I drank boutique drinks in a year on one hand. After interning at a bank for only 5 months, it is safe to say that I have exceeded the amount of drinks I have drank in my entire lifetime.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:20:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/training/</guid>
      
        <description>&amp;ldquo;No man has the right to be an amateur in the matter of physical training. It is a shame for a man to grow old without seeing the beauty and strength of which his body is capable.&amp;rdquo;
Socrates
 I was never an athletic individual. From childhood, I was never pushed to play sports, train, or do a lot of physical activities. Even playing around on the playground was a rare moment of bliss.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tranquility</title>
      <link>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/tranquility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 15:19:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/tranquility/</guid>
      
        <description>The wandering mind knows no rest
LOVELESS, ACT 2
 It is my personal opinion that the smartphone is quite possibly the most damaging device ever invented. Whereas before, to access the global store of knowledge known as the Internet, we had to sit down and open our bulky and heavy computers, now we can easily and quickly access it anywhere. Never before has communication, research, and navigation been so easy.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year</title>
      <link>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/mypost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 12:59:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kmil31.github.io/posts/mypost/</guid>
      
        <description>Days pass by like flowing water.
 The year is ending. Time flows like an unstoppable river, crushing everything within its way until it reaches the ocean. I am 23 years old. The average life expectancy for a male in my demographic is around 72 years old. Without realizing it, I am nearly halfway there. Halfway to an ending. My own father met death at the ripe age of 59.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://kmil31.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kmil31.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      
        <description>Myself Suprisingly not a developer. Really likes tech, animals, performance metrics and music. Always on the lookout for cool new technologies and has a healthy appreciation for everything retro. Hardened soul forged by the fires of time and experience. Varied genre tastes but unabashedly emo, skateboarding and bodyweight fitness.
Skills Fairly fluent in communicating and writing in English. Would love to be more fluent in my beautiful native language, Bahasa Malaysia.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>